[Music]
I'm making a
faun costume for Halloween, and this time the coolest
part came out: the hoof boots! First,
I sculpted the design.
Next, I
mixed up some silicone and then put everything in the
box. Luckily, I had just
enough silicone. After it dried,
I took my model out of the mold,
and then I started
on the
heel. Next, I
filled the silicone mold with smoothcast and
pressed the heel into it. I also attached
a Velcro fastener with hot glue
so I can
remove or replace the tights if needed.
I cut the bottom off the tights
and then attached them to the Velcro with hot glue.
Next, I added faux fur on top,
also with
hot glue, of course. Unfortunately, I didn't manage to spray the tights with the
airbrush very well.
Then I
used acrylic paints to paint the hooves.
This is the finished result,
and apart from the tights, I think it's pretty cool. Feel free to
write
what you think in the comments!